[theme music playing]
Have you heard the news?
Someone from the co-op died.
Yes. Mr. Ramon.
With all the people you had killed,
you might as well be the Grim Reaper.
I only did what I had to do.
You always make decisions
without thinking of the consequences…
so no wonder Grandpa
still can't trust you!
I wish I wasn't born an Ardiente!
I swear I won't come back here
until I prove
you had a hand in Mr. Ramon's death
and the other killings in this town!
I just came here to offer my condolences
and tell you the project is on hold.
Did someone have to die first
before you realize
what you're doing is wrong?
-You monster!
-Mr. Dolfo!
You monster!
-Ivy, wait!
-You're concerned?
[Diego] Do you think I'd ever
let you get hurt?
What he did was wrong.
But, please, don't file charges.
[Ivy] I didn't file charges.
Please forgive me for what I did.
I understand you.
I know how you feel.
I know the pain
of losing someone you love.
[Arnaldo] I saw you two.
Do you think I liked what you did?
Ivy is mine.
And if I see you
hovering around her again…
[clicks tongue]
[Claire] How is your father doing?
[Emilia] I don't want to know.
[Claire] Aren't you excited
for your father
to return alive and limping?
[Emilia] Not now. I'm only just starting.
He has Natalie, Dad!
Why does he even need Ivy?
Why? Do you like Ivy, too?
[Diego] I can't explain
what I feel for her,
but it feels like
I've known her for so long.
I want to get to know her more.
I want to protect her from Arnaldo.
[heart monitor beeping]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Dr. York?
Emilia, it's good to finally talk to you.
Dr. York, how's my dad doing?
He's okay.
Better than okay, actually.
He's recovering faster than expected.
Um… That's good to know.
Does this mean…
Yes.
He'll be coming home soon.
His right index finger
moved earlier today.
That's wonderful, Doc.
I can't wait for him to come home.
He will.
And possibly, without any complications.
He can continue to serve the people.
Thank you, Doc.
Thank you so much
for taking care of my dad.
All right. I think that will be it.
Thank you very much, Emilia.
[tense music playing]
He can't come back yet.
You.
You and your weaknesses as a woman!
-You never think, do you?
-Ouch!
-Show some dignity!
-Ow!
Ouch!
Emilia, you disappoint me.
I don't want to be his slave.
I don't want to be his puppet again.
I understand you, Emilia.
I don't want you
to go through the same thing
my sister did with Julio.
Auntie, I promised Mama
I wouldn't be like her.
[Julio] What?!
You're a disgrace!
You can't even hold a simple event?!
Forgive me, Love. [sobs]
What?!
-"Love"?!
-[crying]
"Mayor"!
Call me "Mayor"! Remember that!
Please forgive me, Mayor.
You couldn't even give me a son,
now you can't even do something
as simple as this for me?!
It won't happen again!
-[sobbing]
-You…
This better not happen again.
Or else you'll suffer worse than this!
[tense music playing]
Ma!
-Ma…
-[crying]
Ma, are you all right?!
How dare you?!
You keep on giving me nothing but…
-shame and disappointment!
-[sobbing]
You shameful woman!
Your mistress got what she deserved!
Whatever relationship
I have with that woman
is none of your business!
I am your wife!
You are just my wife.
It's your fault why I look
for other women!
Just look at yourself!
Who in their right mind would
ever want to sleep with you?!
I became this way because of you!
Oh, so you're blaming me now?
-Stop!
-How dare you?!
That's enough, Papa!
Stay out of this!
-You bitch!
-Ah!
What? Are you fighting back now?!
-[vase shattering]
-Ah!
You little brat.
Are you going against me?!
-No, don't!
-Come here! Come here!
Stop it, Julio!
Hurt me, instead! Not our daughter!
Pa!
Stop it!
[whimpers]
You two can go to hell!
Forgive me, Julio!
Please forgive us! Forgive me!
[sobbing]
Why, Mama?
Why do you let Papa hurt you?
Because I'm just a woman, Emilia.
I'm weak.
[crying]
That's not true, Ma.
[somber music playing]
My time has come, Aunt Claire.
Papa is gone.
He's over.
[ominous music playing]
I am Emilia Ardiente.
I will be the most
powerful woman in this town…
and the entire country.
[ominous music playing]
[soft music playing]
It was just a kiss.
It's no big deal.
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
But I hope you'll forgive me.
Yes, I forgive you.
[soft music playing]
Good, you're still up.
I wanted to talk to you.
About what?
About Diego.
Forget it.
He already apologized. We're fine now.
Wait, what?
You're not mad he kissed you?
Ivy, he disrespected you!
Calm down.
He already said sorry. We're fine now.
Besides, I hit him right after,
if that's what you want to hear.
That's not enough.
I could beat him to a pulp.
I can break a few bones if you want.
Hang on.
Why are you acting like this?
I said we're fine.
Ivy…
I just want to protect
you from the Ardientes.
Especially from those brothers.
Besides…
I promised Ms. Prianka.
I know.
I know that.
It won't happen again.
I'll keep my distance from Arnaldo.
And Diego, too.
You better.
What?
I said, what's your next move?
[Pablo] Yes.
I will make sure it's legislated.
No!
I don't agree.
Listen, let's just meet
when I return to Manila.
Okay? Bye.
[Emilia] Senator.
Emilia.
You know, being a senator
must be so hectic.
-All the phone calls, travels…
-[Pablo chuckles]
It looks exhausting.
Not for the weak.
I know. Too bad Papa
has to give up his dreams.
What do you mean?
I spoke to his doctor last night.
The prognosis of his recovery
doesn't look too good.
[Pablo sighs]
Too bad for Julio then.
I know, Senator.
That's why I'm formally
withdrawing his candidacy
for this election.
I have to forward this to the party.
We'll find a suitable
replacement for him right away.
Come on, Senator.
I repeatedly expressed my interest
in running this election.
Won't you support me?
[Pablo chuckles]
I'm not the only one who decides.
How about this, Senator?
What does the party need
for them to support me?
You know very well
the answer to that, Emilia.
Money?
[chuckles]
Lots of it.
Hmm.
Tell the Land Acquisition Team
to come to Poblacion Ardiente.
I have something I need
to discuss with them.
And…
This one.
Please return it to the Habitat Group.
Tell them it's overpriced.
They should fix it.
Yes, Miss Aguas.
By the way, Governor
Emilia's EA called earlier.
She said she's going to visit.
Okay.
Ivy!
Hi!
-Emilia!
-[Emilia chuckles]
It's nice to see you.
You got here just in time.
I'm arranging EPZ's transfer
to its new site.
Ivy, the EPZ can wait,
but what I have to say can't.
I'm going to replace Dad
and run for Senate!
Yes, Ivy! I'm going to be a senator soon!
And when that happens,
we're both going to be unstoppable!
[chuckles]
Congrats! Con…
Congratulations, Emilia.
Uh…
I'm sorry, but…
What about Arnaldo?
I thought he's the one being
groomed by the congressman?
Ivy, Papa's not here,
so I'm the one who calls the shots.
What if Arnaldo protests?
You know how he is.
He's just like his grandfather.
Then, I will do what I do best.
Whoever goes against Governor Emilia…
Oh, come now, Ivy.
You make it sound like I'm very dangerous.
I'm still a mother.
I can always discipline Arnaldo.
What? Aren't you gonna offer me anything?
We should celebrate!
Oh, you're right. Okay.
-Hold on.
-Thank you.
Nanny Carlotta, please get the champagne.
-Let's celebrate.
-I know!
-Can I sit down?
-Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Of course, you can sit down…
-Senator Emilia.
-[Emilia chuckles]
This is it!
Nanny!
Shoo the flies away.
Oh, no!
[Claire] The eggs are overcooked.
Cook a new batch.
Take this with you.
Take it back to the kitchen.
[cutlery clanking]
Mamita.
Good morning, Arnaldo.
Good morning.
Sorry, we didn't see
each other last night.
I was tired.
It was such a long flight.
It's okay. Uh…
How are you?
I'm fine.
Still beautiful, I suppose.
I can see that.
By the way…
Your mom told me about you and Diego.
Arnaldo…
I want you to patch things up with Diego.
You know how high your mother's
political dreams are.
And your sibling rivalry
will not help her one bit.
Mamita, save it.
Diego's the one who should
apologize 'cause I'm the mayor.
He should follow and
respect everything I want.
But let's not talk about him.
Let's talk about you.
I haven't seen you in so long.
Well, let's eat.
[unsettling music playing]
What do you want me to do with him?
Just keep his therapy going.
Doc, once he gets better…
Please bring him to this address.
I'll handle it.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Loring] There. Okay.
-Put it down there.
-[Diego grunts]
Hold on, Nanny.
Why? What's wrong?
I need a break.
-[Diego huffs]
-Are you tired?
Water, Nanny?
Drink up, boy.
I'm fine.
Loring?
-Loring.
-Yes?
Mr. Dolfo?
-What brings you here?
-Diego!
I wanted to ask a favor.
What is it?
Can you help me bring these
to Miss Ivy's house?
I just want to thank her.
Sure thing. No problem.
Thank you very much.
Diego! Diego!
-Hey, Butchoy!
-Butchoy!
I want to come, too.
I want to give this to Miss Beautiful.
It's her favorite.
[Loring and Dolfo coo]
[Loring chuckles]
All right. I'll give it to her.
Diego. come closer.
-He has more.
-What?
I have a letter for her.
Wow!
Hey, aren't you a little
too young for love letters?
You're something else, huh?
Someone might beat me to her.
[Loring] That's right.
[imitating Butchoy]
Someone here just might.
Right?
[cooing]
Arnaldo, join us.
Good evening.
Are we celebrating something, Mom?
I'm glad you mentioned it.
As a matter of fact, we are.
Senator Pablo spoke to me.
And it's final, I'm running for Senate.
[tense music playing]
But, Mom…
Arnaldo, it's final.
Senator Pablo already spoke to me.
You know how hard it is to refuse him.
Arnaldo, look.
Now is my time.
And when your time comes,
I'll be your greatest supporter.
But for now, I need your support.
[tense music playing]
Excuse me.
Arnaldo?
Arnaldo!
Let's eat.
[tense music playing]
I have to stop Emilia.
I can't let her run for senator.
If she wins,
she'll have the power
to manipulate our judicial system.
It'll be hard to seek justice
if that happens.
What will you do?
Ivy.
Jepoy.
Have you found them?
Arthur's already recovering safely.
We have Tonio, too.
-Nice! My cards are great.
-I quit. I have a bad draw.
You're such a spoilsport.
-We struck gold again.
-All right!
-That looks good!
-I know!
That's not even enough for Mario.
[laughs]
That's why we should just behave,
and the Ardientes will
take care of us, right?
-Yeah.
-Right.
[goon 1] I don't wanna end up like Tonio.
Who's Tonio?
Oh, right, he doesn't know him.
He was the governor's number one hit man.
He was still the mayor then, right?
Have you heard anything about him?
[goon 2] The governor
probably had killed him.
He knew too much.
[Ivy] Good.
But we need more evidence.
I do have some evidence,
but it's not enough.
I have Emilia on record admitting
her family runs the town's
illegal gambling dens.
But I need more whistleblowers
against Emilia.
And we will use that evidence
to strengthen our testimony
and take down the Ardientes.
Since Arthur is recovering,
he's still no good to us.
What about Tonio?
You know what to do.
But Ivy…
What is it this time?
There you go again, Jepoy!
Thank you for your concern.
You just want to protect me.
I know that already!
But I need you to do this.
You're the only one I can trust
when it comes to Tonio.
So, please, set those
concerns aside for now.
Go on.
If you have to,
ask for a leave from Arnaldo,
so you can focus on your task.
Jepoy, don't give me that look.
Go!
All right.
I still have a lot of work to do.
[unsettling music playing]
[phone ringing]
-[sighs]
-[phone ringing]
Senator?
Good evening, Miss Aguas.
I'd like to invite you out
for dinner, Miss Aguas.
Are you free?
It depends on what the dinner is for.
I'm sure Emilia already approached you…
…regarding her senatorial ambition.
Let me guess.
Emilia spoke to you
to convince me to support her.
No, Miss Aguas.
On the contrary…
I have a different candidate in mind.
I want you to support them.
A different candidate?
I like the sound of that.
Okay, Senator.
Text me which restaurant.
I'll be there.
Nanny, I won't be having dinner here.
I need to meet with the senator.
I think he's going along with my plan.
All right, dear.
I'll go get changed.
Please take care.
[unsettling music playing]
Grandpa?
Can you hear me?
It's Arnaldo, your favorite grandson.
Please wake up, Grandpa.
I need you here.
Mom's getting out of control.
I don't know what to do anymore.
[Julio] I had this made for you, Arnaldo.
You have to study this,
till you can control every piece of it
from wherever you are.
That is the mark of a true leader.
When I'm gone, all this will be yours.
You will be the king
of Poblacion Ardiente.
Take good care of our name.
I promise, Grandpa.
[sighs]
I won't fail you.
I will protect the interest of our name,
no matter what.
[exhales sharply]
[ominous music playing]
[heart monitor beeping]
[bright music playing]
[Loring and Pandoy snickering]
Looks like you're off to court someone.
-Court someone?
-Hmm?
I'm just going to deliver
Mr. Dolfo and Butchoy's gifts to Ivy.
Well, at least Butchoy isn't afraid…
-to show his feelings.
-That's right.
Exactly.
I'm not afraid, okay?
[both] Oh?
Then prove it.
[Loring and Pandoy giggling]
You'd like that, huh?
But how can he prove it?
He's not going there to court her.
He's just dropping off
a letter and some flowers
from Butchoy.
Because Butchoy isn't shy!
-He's serious about her!
-You're so silly!
[Pandoy] Then why dress up
just to deliver flowers?
-He's looking sharp.
-Oh, stop it, will you?
Hey! Why are you blushing?
What?!
-No, I'm not!
-[laughter]
[giggling]
[laughing and cooing]
-[Diego] I have to go.
-He's excited!
We're just admiring how handsome you are.
This is special.
-Hmm?
-Ooh?
Quit it, you two.
I'll just text you, Nanny.
Okay. Please take care.
I will.
Butchoy, Mr. Dolfo, ma'am…
Diego…
What are you doing here?
Ivy, they said they wanted
to give you something.
For you, Miss Ivy.
[Dolfo] Thank you very much.
I'm really sorry for what I did, ma'am.
Mr. Dolfo, we already talked about this.
I understand how you felt.
But thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Just put it down here.
And you?
Why are you here?
For you, Miss Beautiful.
[chuckles]
You're so cute!
And you're so sweet, too!
Thank you for these.
Mr. Dolfo, let's go back to the car.
[chuckles softly]
Hey, Butchoy!
Your other gift!
You give it to her, Diego!
Uh…
[chuckles]
Butchoy has a love letter for you.
A love letter? [chuckles]
He's so cute.
I guess…
I've got more competition now.
What?
[soft music playing]
I said, he's too young for that.
[Ivy] Oh.
Ah, yes.
Butchoy is still too young
to think about love.
And…
You know, love is just a distraction.
Especially from important things.
Like Butchoy's studies.
Anyway, Diego, I have to go.
I have an appointment.
Butchoy, Mr. Dolfo, ma'am?
I'll be going now.
-Bye! Take care!
-Take care, Diego.
Thank you for coming, Miss Aguas.
Why am I here again, Senator?
It's about the Ardientes.
I'm worried, especially about Emilia.
She's been making
a fool of herself lately.
Ah. Senator…
Be careful.
I'm Emilia's friend.
I might just tell her what you said.
[chuckles]
You won't do that.
Because you don't play
that way, Miss Aguas.
[chuckles]
So…
Emilia must've approached you
about replacing Julio in the senate race.
And you have a problem with that because?
Because…
She isn't ready.
I'm afraid how it could possibly affect me
and the whole party
if her endorsement pushes through.
Senator, the solution is very simple.
Don't endorse her.
It's not that easy.
And you need me to make it easy? Hmm?
[laughs]
Very smart, Miss Aguas.
What will I gain from this, Senator?
I'll support you…
in your future business endeavors.
I'll even bend some rules
for you, Miss Aguas,
if that's what you need.
Senator, I can handle my own.
But…
If I say yes…
what would I have to do?
What would you like me to do?
I want you to support Arnaldo.
[tense music playing]
You're free for tonight, Madrigal.
Report to me tomorrow.
I'd like to ask
for your permission, Mayor.
I have to go to Manila
for a family emergency.
How long will you be gone?
About two days.
-Sure.
-Thank you, Mayor.
Make sure you're going to your family.
I don't like being betrayed
by the people I trust.
[tense music playing]
[Pablo] A lot of people say
he's too young.
But I believe in him.
Julio trained him, after all.
Wow.
Arnaldo and Emilia…
You want to pit the son
against his mother, Senator?
Exactly.
And competitions like this…
produce good results.
You will benefit
from this, too, Miss Aguas.
As long as I won't get caught in between.
I will make sure of that.
You owe me.
And I am generous…
when it comes to returning
favors, Miss Aguas.
[glasses clink]
Arnaldo versus Emilia.
[chuckles]
Why the long face?
What happened?
Huh?
Well, I just gave Ivy
what I had to give her.
But you couldn't say what you needed to.
-Hmm?
-Exactly, Uncle.
I ended up saying things I shouldn't have.
-Hmm?
-Huh? What do you mean?
[Loring] You mean like…
"I love you, are you okay?"
-Nanny, that's not it.
-[chuckling]
Well, Diego, what exactly
did you want to tell Miss Ivy?
-We are getting really confused.
-Yeah.
[Loring] Okay, look.
First, you were always fighting.
And then you made up
and became friendly.
Then you were fighting again.
But you saved her.
Then you fought again.
And then…
We don't know what happened after.
And now we see you getting all dressed up
just to visit her.
Is there something you're not telling us?
[deep sigh]
-Hmm?
-Oh?
He's blushing. I guess there's something.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
-Uh…
Let's just say I want us
to be friends first
so we could know each other better.
Let's leave it at that.
Ah…
But what if…
What if Lily returns?
[soft music playing]
-Nanny.
-Ivy.
How did it go?
By the way, Joan called.
She'll be here by 9 tomorrow
for your meeting.
Have some tea first.
Thank you.
My dinner with the senator went well.
I got what I needed.
And since Jepoy won't be here tomorrow,
I'll take care of the farmers'
problem with their land.
I'm sure Diego and the farmers
will be glad.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
I'll just have tea next time.
I'm going to bed.
-Okay, then.
-Good night.
Good night, dear.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
[Loring] But what if…
What if Lily returns?
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
It's been 13 years since you left.
[Butchoy] Dear Miss Beautiful,
I just want to thank you
for all the help you've given us.
I also want to thank you
for teaching me to be brave.
And even though I'm weak and fat,
you still think I'm cute.
I promise to exercise more,
so I'll be as fit and handsome as Diego.
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary
continues playing]
It's been 13 years.
We had beautiful memories together.
But I have to forget you, Diego.
I spoke to Daddy earlier, and he told me
that the political party
is considering you…
to run for senator in the next election.
What?
Meaning, I'll be replacing Grandpa?
Well…
If your mom backs out,
or if they don't choose her.
Okay, that's weird.
Mom said the party
already chose to endorse her.
Daddy didn't mention that.
Maybe Aunt Emilia misinterpreted it.
Maybe.
But I'll take this seriously.
I'll make sure the party
is going to endorse me.
[chuckles]
That's my boyfriend.
That's my future senator.
And that's my future husband.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you.
You're so powerful.
[ominous music playing]
This deed of donation is not valid.
Julio Ardiente's father did not sign it.
And since he's long dead…
this is useless.
[tense music playing]
And the congressman…
transferred this property to
Arnaldo Ardiente ten years ago.
That's why he's the key
to legally transferring
the land ownership
directly to the farmers.
Yes, Miss Aguas.
Mr. Torillo can draft a
new deed of donation
for the farmers.
Leave that to me.
Joan, can you attend to my other concerns?
Like the property I want to buy.
It's named under…
Attorney Dante Cruz.
Yes, Miss Aguas. I'm on top of it.
Okay, we're done here. Thank you.
-Thank you.
Thank you, ma'am.
[tense music playing]
[bright music playing]
[bright music continues playing]
I want to give this to Miss Beautiful.
It's her favorite.
[music fading]
[giggling]
Mr. Mayor.
[Arnaldo] Miss Aguas.
Sorry, um…
What are you doing here?
How dare you show your face
to me after what you did.
Mr. Mayor, I need to consult
something with you.
Aww.
Too bad!
You don't have an appointment.
-Why don't you just leave?
-[Ivy chuckles]
Mr. Mayor, I didn't know you had
a new secretary and…
a new nanny.
-What?!
-Natalie.
Please, please, no.
Don't do that.
It's my fault.
I forgot to put my meeting
with Miss Aguas in my schedule.
So, you can go now. I have to work.
You should leave now.
[Natalie] I'm not leaving.
Who knows what that woman might do to you?
It's okay, Mr. Mayor.
I'll leave.
I don't want to discuss important matters
in front of insignificant people.
-Bye.
-No, no, no, Miss Aguas.
-Uh, Natalie…
-It's okay.
No, no, no, no. Natalie is about to leave.
-Are you sure?
-Natalie.
She's about to leave.
Natalie, I'm the mayor of this town, okay?
I have responsibilities to take care of.
And as my girlfriend,
I'm sure you understand and respect that.
Right?
Okay?
[tense music playing]
Okay.
For you, I'll go.
[Arnaldo] Thank you.
I am sorry about that, but, ah…
Such a brat!
I know. But I must say…
you made me lie again, Miss Aguas.
Really?
I don't think so.
I mean, who kept texting me,
telling me he wanted to see me?
Why did you want to see me, Mr. Mayor?
Okay.
I want to be a senator.
And I need your help.
What?
You're going against Emilia?
She's your mom.
I know.
But in our family,
it doesn't work that way.
To us, men will always
be superior to women.
It doesn't look like Emilia knows that.
Okay, I'll get straight to the point.
There are many reasons
why I don't want her
to run in place of Grandpa.
First of all, her stubborn
and reckless attitude
will be our family's undoing.
She will exhaust our money
because I know for a fact
that she will lose.
She will ruin our family's name,
and I won't let her put all of
Grandpa's efforts to waste.
Miss Aguas, I was born to lead.
And this is my chance.
I need your help.
So, how can I help?
I like that question.
With the campaign funds…
that you promised my grandfather.
[chuckles]
Well, I'll think about it, Mr. Mayor.
Because to be honest…
I'd rather support Emilia than you.
What can I do to change your mind?
[sultry music playing]
The farmers' land…
Aren't they in your name?
I want it.
Give it to me.
Are you doing this
for the farmers or for Diego?
Because I'll be honest with you.
I'm jealous of the attention
you're giving my brother.
Well, Mr. Mayor, it's not my fault
if your brother moves…
faster than you do.
[scoffs]
Okay.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I like you, Miss Aguas.
I really like you.
Mr. Mayor…
I know that.
But of course,
I can't be yours because…
you already have Natalie.
And you can't win the prize…
if you don't give me what I want.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
It's Emilia calling.
-[phone ringing]
-I almost forgot.
-We have a meeting for…
-[phone ringing]
her senatorial bid.
Bye, Mr. Mayor.
[tense music playing]
You have to give me what I want…
before you get the prize.
So, I just had to inform you
that I found a new site
for the EPZ project.
I'll have the team discuss it with you
when your schedule permits it.
I don't want to focus on that, Ivy.
I want to focus on me.
Okay.
Where is the support you
promised my father's candidacy?
Yes, I'm still supporting your father.
Well then, I want you
to fulfill that promise.
Where's the money? Give it to me.
Emilia, relax.
I said I'd support your father.
Not you.
Ivy, I'm replacing my father.
I'm not so sure, Emilia.
You see, that's…
That's not what I heard
from your son, the Mayor.
Tell me.
Emilia…
Yes, I'm your friend.
But I don't want any trouble.
Maybe…
you should just ask your son.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
TRANSFER CERTIFICATE OF TITLE
ARNALDO ARDIENTE TORILLO
Arnaldo?
What's that?
Nothing.
Just some files I had Grandpa sign before.
See you, Mom.
Are you sure? What's that
you're keeping from me?
Nothing. I don't keep anything from you.
Okay, because I don't like you
keeping secrets from me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
EPZ INVESTOR IVY AGUAS
FARMER'S HERO
What newspaper is that, Auntie?
The one from Ardiente.
It has a picture of…
a woman.
Her name's Ivy Aguas.
She's really interested in it.
She keeps looking at it.
Okay, here's what you should do.
Observe her closely.
If she says or does anything strange,
call me right away.
[Belen] When will you be back?
I don't know yet.
Emilia's watching my every move.
All right.
I'll keep an eye on her.
[unsettling music playing]
Who were you talking to, Raul?
[dramatic music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[Arnaldo] I'm a man
of my word, Miss Aguas.
I hope you are, too.
[Natalie] You just won't stop
flirting with my boyfriend, huh?
Choose. Is it Ivy?
Or my daddy's support
for your senatorial ambition.
[Emilia] Well, I called this meeting
to correct some mistakes.
Arnaldo doesn't know
that Dad already gave that to me,
so I had it transferred under my name.
Raul, you need to get back here right now.
[Raul] Why? What happened to her?
I think she's coming back to her senses.
[Ivy] What are we doing here?
[Diego] Didn't I say I'd bring you
somewhere a little more peaceful?
[gunshot]
[theme music playing]